julian-fashion.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy - US

**DISCLOSURE PURSUANT TO ART. 13 and 14 OF THE EUROPEAN REGULATION 679/2016 (GDPR)**

Here at Julian Fashion, we are committed to the protection of our clients’ personal data and their privacy. This Privacy Policy intends to detail how we process this data. The term “personal data” is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as “ _any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('Data Subject')_ ”, such as surnames, email addresses and other information that identify a person or render them identifiable. 

Purposes of Processing Personal Data

Julian Fashion processes clients’ personal information mainly for purposes of allowing them access, registration and purchases.

Any further processing takes place only on the basis of obligations established by law, or with the explicit consent given by the User to the Owner.

In particular, Julian Fashion collects and processes the personal data of Users for the following purposes:

  1. To respond to requests from Users sent via the Site;
  2. To fulfill orders;
  3. To fulfill legal or fiscal obligations pursuant to current legislation;
  4. Communicate, with the Users’ consent, through different channels to offer them commercial offers and promotions

Personal data may be processed via either paper or digital means (including portable devices) and appropriate security measures are taken to protect them and guarantee their confidentiality and integrity and are processed strictly for the purposes detailed above. 

Consequences of the Failure to Communicate Personal Data

The failure to communicate personal data necessary for the fulfillment of the sales contract or a legal obligation (such as those related to the keeping of accounting & tax records) will impede the fulfillment of said sales contract.

Data Retention

Personal Data processed by Julian Fashion under the User’s consent will be retained exclusively for the time needed to achieve the purpose for which they were originally collected or until the consent for their processing is revoked.

For further information with regards to the criteria and timing of the storage of your data, please contact our Data Protection Officer at [**privacy@julian-fashion.com**](mailto:privacy@julian-fashion.com)

Sharing Your Data

Julian Fashion shall not share its clients’ personal data with third parties, internal or external, unless it is absolutely necessary for the fulfillment of the sales contract and under the clients’ consent, with the adequate security measures taken to ensure their integrity.

In accordance with the new EU Regulation UE 2016/679 on Data Protection (GDPR), the data may be transferred to non EU countries or countries not belonging to the European Economic Area, that however grant an adequate level of protection of the personal data.As far as the processing of credit cards' data is concerned, Easy Nolo will appoint the Riskified Ltd. company as sub-manager of data processing. In any case, the data processing will take place in accordance with the provisions of the current rules and regulations.

Client Rights

Among the rights granted to you by this Privacy Regulation are:

  * Requesting access to your personal data, correction of inaccurate data or completing incomplete data, erasure of your data (upon the occurrence of one of the conditions indicated in article 17, paragraph 1 of the GDPR and in compliance with the exceptions provided for in paragraph 3 of the same article), the limitation of the processing of your personal data (upon the use of one of the hypotheses indicated in Article 18, paragraph 1 of the GDPR);
  * Requesting and obtaining portability of your personal data (where applicable);
  * Opposing at any point in time the processing of your personal data with regards to the occurrence of certain situations that might affect you;
  * Revoking the consent given to processing your data at any point in time by communicating your request via e-mail at [**privacy@julian-fashion.com**](mailto:privacy@julian-fashion.com). The processing of your data prior to the revocation of consent remains lawful however.
  * Submitting complaints to supervisory authorities, where the conditions exist.

Data Controller and Data Protection Officer

Julian Fashion s.r.l is the Data Controller and service provider with its office located in Viale Matteotti n. 31- 45015 Milano Marittima (RA)

For any questions related to our website, please contact [**customercare@julian-fashion.com**](mailto:customercare@julian-fashion.com); for information relative to processing personal data or privacy please contact the Data Protection Officer at [**privacy@julian-fashion.com**](mailto:privacy@julian-fashion.com)

 Changes and Updates

The present policy is valid from May 25, 2018. Changes and/or additions may be made by Julian Fashion also as a consequence of any subsequent changes and/or regulatory additions to the Privacy Regulations.
